You have to keep an eye on this as well.
You will also see this counter-reacting to the results. Vishwesh
ji, please look at the chart of ICI Lombard.
Its numbers came almost as per the estimates yesterday.
Sir, Deepanshu, see, the numbers are as per the estimates, but the
stock has not performed in the near term.
If you look at the highs of July, they
were around 1380. Recently, it went up to 00 and that
too was given up. So, technically, you
can assume that the
stock has not done anything in almost nine odd months. I
believe that this stock has potential.
However, considering the market trend,
I think that if it reaches 1330, then I
think it becomes a great investment pick with a profit of Rs 10,000
because it
is fundamentally strong and it has to go up
to the level of 1500. So, Deepansh, my
advice would be that if it gets below the
range of 1330-1310, then it should be considered there. I
think that would be the lower end of the
range.  While many
things have increased in the market, there are some pockets which have
not performed yet. ICC Lord is
one of them, so definitely buy on decline
but the view will be from medium term point of view. We are
buy on decline but let's take a medium term
or positional view on this, let's see
what reaction it gets today. It can be an
interesting day in trading for this counter
also.